No, no, no
My morals scream at me from the depths of my brain,
"Don't do it, you idiot"
Darlin' baby, darlin
I love you like crazy!
It's a philosophy that's got me giddy and sparking with anticipation
The way you look up at me is so adorable
It just kills me, it's almost illegal
Scattering madness,
I'd squandered it all
Before I knew it and your existence is to blame
Don't care if it's fake
Give me everything with your name on it right now
I love yous spew from my carotid artery
ABYSS OUT
What the hell am I supposed to do about these feelings?
In the back of my ribs
Sugar crystals melt, ready to ooze into puke
BOOM
My pupils dilated to the max, I feel like I'm about to drown
In this world right now, you're my one-and-only perfect answer